No-Bake Brownie Bars. 45 min · 16 servings · American
Ingredients: 10. 3/4 cup peanut butter (or any nut or seed butter); 1/3 cup maple syrup (or honey); 3 tbs coconut oil (or olive oil); 1 tsp vanilla extract
Section: Bars
Step 1. Line a 13x9 inch sheet pan with parchment paper.
Step 2. In a medium bowl, whisk together the peanut butter, maple syrup, oil and vanilla. Add in the sifted cacao powder, almond flour, mini chips and salt a…
Step 3. Transfer the dough to your prepped pan and spread out evenly with your hands, to form a rectangular shape that's about 1/2 inch thick.
Section: Topping
Step 4. Melt your chips and oil in a small pot and pour this onto the brownie rectangle. Using a small rubber spatula, spread out the ganache evenly.
Step 5. Transfer this pan to your freezer for about 40 minutes to set. Remove and slice into 16 squares. Store leftovers in an airtight container in your fre…
You're ready. Use Make It for checkboxes on the page.